- First of all, we make this look easy.
Us black girls with all kinds of curls,
smellin' of cocoa butter
out here every damn day
savin' the world.
(audience chattering)
- Time and time again we find the ways
and means between packin'
lunches, planning launches,
and pattin' weaves
- [Audience Member] Yeah!
- to get information to stay in formation.
Girl, you heard what they sayin'?
Ain't no games to be
playin', so we show up
and show out and turn up and
♪ Turn this mutha out ♪
and flip it and Yazmin, throw side eyes,
gather, get folks all the way together
with edges still in place,
skin defying time and space.
They call it Black Girl
Magic cause ain't no way
to explain our
♪ Amazing grace ♪
(audience cheering)
How sweet the sound of a
black girl's point of view.
Knowing that nobody
does it like we do boo.
Pride in our power,
strength in our strides.
You can attempt to imitate
but soul you cannot buy.
(audience yelling)
We work twice as hard and
must be twice as perfect.
Purvey is a potent truth
we deliver in small doses.
Cause folks is shook when she's movin'.
Oh no, it's another angry black woman.
Bunk that, we're not hostile.
We're passionate, clapping back is our way
of declaring we ain't havin' it.
(audience cheering)
They go low, we go high.
They say no, we devy.
They didn't want us to read, kept us out
of libraries they built, now
we are the biggest buyers
of books so we can read you for filth.
(audience cheering)
Our magic is in our love and tears,
our fears and our
fly-ness, our sisterhoods
and insecurities are ride
or don't even try it.
We are not the one and still we rise.
- [Audience Member] Yeah.
- This here is for colored
girls who've considered
gettin' your life and
are reclaiming our time.
(audience cheering)
(fast tempo music)